Heat. Hey, Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Ah, hello everyone.
Hello. Hello.
Kama, it's been a while.
How has everyone been? Hello. Hello. I
haven't
I haven't live streamed for like a week
now, right? It's crazy, isn't it?
[laughter]
Hello. Hello.
Um, I'm able.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
[music]
[laughter]
Uh, translation.
I know it's late for me. It's 11:00 p.m.
It's really late. So, I thought um I'll
play our creators for a little bit. Just
a little bit. A little little bit.
And before I go sleep,
why did your say hi, Lord? I wasn't even
there. Hey. Oh, wait. Didn't you type
WTF?
Oh, wait, wait, wait. It's from the
other one. Oh, the other live stream is
there now. Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. The other one is there
now. Okay. Oh, I forgot.
Oh. Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. [laughter]
Oh, yeah. I forgot the other one. I
forgot to end that one. I was still
testing out things, right?
Um,
hello Suku Sukun Sukuna
is Salvation. Welcome to the stream.
Welcome.
Hello. Hello.
Uh, I might change stuff so we can read
chat.
Uh,
Oh, these are old, huh? Okay. Anyway,
hi. Uh, oh, yeah. Uh, Discord
announcement did not get sent through,
right? Let me force send it. I was
working on this yesterday, so it should
technically make a new announcement.
Uh,
why is it not doing it?
[laughter and gasps]
Don't tell me.
Uh why
bro? Brother, what? What?
What the Why is it not sending the fear,
bro?
Oh, this stupid thing. I have to fix it
again.
Okay, let me see if it checks. Okay.
Yeah, when you have two mult streams
running on your channel, one is a
unlisted stream and one is a public
stream, it messes up everything, I
guess.
Wow, that's so weird.
Any uh so yeah, I thought of playing our
creators today. Um game is open, I
believe. Let's pray and hope my PC does
not give up or give up.
Allah, I don't want you to die on me
today.
I just hope and pray that it does
actually
uh work. Let me close my browser
just in case. What is this? 86 none. Who
are you? Oh my god.
The moment I go live, issues happen.
Command line 86.
Who is in 86? What the heck, bro? Let me
stream peacefully. You're supposed to
announce and stuff.
86. Uh,
target.
Oh,
not. What do you mean by there's no
horizontal ID, brother?
Oh my lord. Horizontal. Hurry. Hurry.
Horizontal lady. It is literally there.
What?
Horizontal.
I want to I want to
fine.
Cream
registry. [sighs]
How is it breaking like this? You're not
supposed to be broken like this. I don't
get it. Just work.
Undefined.
[crying]
Who is this undefined? Wait. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my
god. I swear to God. [laughter]
Let me Okay, you know what? I have an
idea. I have an idea. Okay. Uh, copy the
whole damn thing.
Put it here.
Comma. Paste the thing
and name it as undefined.
Undefined.
Now you're supposed to work. Please
[laughter]
wait. What the Where's work? Okay, let
me run it again.
Why now? Bucka.
Okay. Game. Okay. Wait. Uh. Oh god, my
PC is dying. Oh, no. No. No. No. No. No.
[laughter]
No,
brother. What?
Wait, you don't see even see the You
don't even see the game though.
Art crus wait m Why is it not audable?
Huh?
Art creators I give you. Oh, there you
go. Okay, position four. Okay, I got
higher rank, right? Wilder three.
Okay, new things came in.
Nice.
Today I thought we'll do this and um
yeah, we'll do this and then
maybe do a few bit of demotion. What?
Oh, I'm here. Okay. Okay, I'm going to
get Daredevil. Oh, nice.
Oh, nice.
I haven't touched this game for a while.
I have to
uh play a lot.
Uh while I haven't streamed this game
for a few while, um I'll tell you what I
did. Uh my uh gear bench is level three
finally. And uh
uh
yeah, I just need a motor for refinery
three. And I just need one more for
rocketeer and medical lab. This guy
needs a lot. And sentininal core is
another stuff I need to get.
So I need Oh yeah. What's the uh trials
for this week? Download information
inside the bunker.
Hm. Interesting.
No. What is this?
>> Okay, before I do this, let me double
check
uh something 333.
Uh
delete. Okay. Okay.
Uh it did not get sent.
Uh,
let me run this. Please work. Please
work.
Why is current live streams just one o?
Uh,
it has to do the thing. Uh,
okay. Uh, let me close
um this.
Oh my god, my PC is dying. Dying.
Come close this.
Did I make the announcement? Okay, I
died. I died.
Uh
uh.
What the? Uh, close this.
Okay. Uh, I need more FPS.
Uh, close this. Why do I even have Riot
Games open? [laughter]
Oh, yeah. I wanted to um I wanted to get
the I wanted to update Valerant cuz the
new something's happening and the new
gun came out in Valerant.
Uh
yeah.
What the heck? Why is it taking forever
to run?
This is the thing. I have so much behind
the scenes stuff
which runs the whole stream and
everything and the moment one or another
fails, every single thing fails.
And I hate it.
I pretty much hate that.
Uh
yeah, me too. I haven't also done it.
I can't read kick chat. I'm sorry. Uh
the stupid way. I want to see. Oh, I can
see quick chat. Okay. Okay. Oh, never
mind. I you I'll use YouTube uh OBS.
Uh close this.
Uh
what's going on today?
uncovered cases.
But the thing is there's no blue the
locked event is not there. You have to
keep an eye on it or something. No.
Okay, let's strategize this.
Okay, my PC is dying dying, bro.
OBS, I'm cing overloaded.
Okay, let me see. Um,
one second.
Destroy pops. We can do that. Yeah,
hornet. The best way is to uh get the
snitch. Let it spawn the hornet. That's
easier way to kill
hornets. But I need like a big good gun.
Purple tier gun. No shock thing.
Ah, rocketeers. Oh lord.
Can Oh, this is easier. I can use the
dams now.
Dams will be a good map to
do it. Yeah. Yeah. Dams will be good map
to do it. Yeah.
Yeah. Dams will be a good map to do
this. Yeah. Yeah.
Give me a minute.
So processing days are expected
patience or book
Invalid body for bro.
I am going to kill some. [laughter] Oh
my god.
Oh my
brother. What?
Nalani.
What do you mean by null? Who in the
[laughter]
wait?
Bro, what the heck? Okay. Horizondo.
>> Oh my god.
Ah, not bad. Let me stream peacefully.
Stupid things.
If I only had an easy way to make it.
God dang it. Why
should have made another testing stream
and tested everything before I went
live, bro? [snorts] Honestly.
Anyway, let's start the game.
I'll be here stuck. Oh yeah. Yeah. Oh.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. I got a torrent
blueprint last run. I forgot. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh forgot. Oh yeah. I got good stuff,
right? Yeah. I forgot. I was killing
like
stuff, [laughter]
bro. It's so cool. Okay, I'll take that
and that.
Uh,
did Yeah. Did you finish the expiration?
I need a good stuff for expedition.
Okay, nice.
A purple attachment.
You know what? I'm going to uh sell one
gun. Okay.
>> I want to go free load out, man.
Bro,
my stuff is so full. Why do I delete
Bastion? So, I can sell Bastion. So, I
finished it, right?
Uh
oh yeah, I can uh sell these as well.
I just Oh, level 75. Nice.
I I need a grind more.
I have my exam, Japanese exams coming
up, so I don't have time now.
Oh yeah, I have to use the keys.
Why do I have snowballs over here? Oh my
god.
No wonder I don't have space.
[laughter]
Baka,
no wonder.
Um,
B.
More. More more.
Got to do a lot.
Is it still matchmaking? 1 minute. Oh my
god.
Sure.
Okay. Wait. Okay. Finally. Let's go.
B78
378.
I don't need this stuff.
Save.
Uh oh. No, no, no. Oh, no.
>> Hope you're close for the season,
Raider. It's a good day for picking
candle,
but do beware of frostbite.
Ah, frostbite.
Uh, is there anything I can do here?
Well, bus is fine apparently.
Okay, there's some people.
Uh, give me a moment again.
I apologize.
Uh,
uh, save
run.
Oh my [sighs] god.
Create the stupid announcement. Dio,
please.
Yes.
Yes. Okay. Finally, this gun
announcement happened. Okay. Finally.
Oh my god.
Okay, I'll fix the issues. I found the
issues. I'll fix them. Wait, is the is
the Discord even running?
Bro, that's not even running. Ah, I'll
let it be. It'll automatically run.
Save.
Okay, next trail. I'll make sure these
um you it won't Okay, someone's doing
the rocket there. Let me go.
that way.
Don't let the doctor die. I want a I
want a piece of it. I want the piece of
it. Please don't let the rocketeer die.
Don't let the rocketeer die.
>> Don't shoot.
Where is it? I hear it.
I want to damage it.
Raider refuge.
Oh, northeast.
Where? Ah, I see you.
I need a little bit of fuel so I can
craft some stuff
under there.
>> Don't shoot.
I am dead there, bro.
Oh sh.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
>> Where's the lock of deer?
Better.
>> Wait, someone's sniping, right?
>> Hey, don't shoot. Hello there.
>> HELLO.
What is that?
Oh, wait. Someone unlocked this.
Will I get shot?
Oh, nice, nice, nice. I don't need that.
I need this.
Can we extract
Oh my god, there's chaos happening.
Hey there. Okay.
Hey, RAIDER.
UH,
my PC is lagging again.
I hate that.
Oh.
Should
I extract? I have 31.
I do want to
pop caros
formats. Now I do wish to do that.
that thingy.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Oh, they left.
Controlled.
All position shut down.
Okay,
we'll extract here and reset.
Don't shoot.
>> Hey there.
>> Hey, Raider.
You are clear.
>> Let's go.
Okay,
we need to strategize better regarding
the trials.
The trial stuff. How can I do it?
trials,
dude. It's 11:40. Yeah, I know. I just
wanted to like stream even though it's
late. Hello, Sappy.
Yeah, we got some good stuff.
Uh,
I'll sell this
like I will stick stuff for my this
thing.
Um,
and
take a lot of bandages. Yes.
Okay, we'll do normal stuff. Okay, I
think that's better. We'll do
tower key. Okay, I'll take one tower key
and
uh shield, right? And the shields. Uh,
I need some adrenaline.
Wait, I can get the looter argument now.
Argument, right?
So, uh,
what the where is it? Gear revenge.
Yeah, I can get this. How much?
Cautious. Now, I want the survivor one
though.
the more loot I can put the more the
better.
Oh yeah.
Go with the hair this time cuz why not?
I'm saving on money.
I'm saving.
[laughter]
I'm going to go with the hair pin. I'm
going to go with the hair pin
also for expedition.
For expedition, let me dump some stuff.
Combat items. We could dump some
baretta.
No. Yeah. Bleta.
Survival items. We can dump some I'll
dam
items.
Huh? Uh, I'll d one of you.
Materials wise, I will um,
everything is important now. Uh,
driver, I don't need it. I'll dam you.
I need more storage. No, there's also
one. That's one. Another.
And we'll craft some ammo.
400 of them.
100. Good.
Uh,
we'll go like this. Uh, medium light kit
kit
and let's go. Uh, oh, there's a magnetic
event going on. Oh,
and trash.
Oh, wait. Lock gate is next after this.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh. Okay, we are
doing that. We are doing that. Okay,
let's go to them.
Uh
electromagnetic it is. Okay,
I don't uh if I'm going in hot,
I believe I would need some bandages.
I'll take that and let's go.
We're supposed to kill the pops, right?
I know a place where I can do that.
Uh,
is 24.
Wait a minute.
Okay, I'm back.
>> Hello.
>> Oh god, it's a late raid.
>> If you're outdoors,
>> let's go to water treatment control.
Oh, wait. Mushrooms.
I'll take those.
I'll take those mushrooms. Yep.
Should have taken more adrenaline.
What the heck?
Oh,
hello Ama. Ma, welcome. What language is
that?
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my
god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
No, no, no.
Oh my god.
>> Hey, don't shoot,
>> brother.
I am having the baddest play ever.
How? How? How?
Dang it.
There's nothing good here.
Don't shoot.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Oh my god.
>> Hey, don't shoot. Thanks.
>> THANKS.
Oh my god. Uh
together.
>> Is that nothing?
There is nothing.
Oh, they all loaded all of this.
Hello, Amber. Welcome. Welcome to the
stream.
I'll do this.
Uh, okay.
I do feel like I could
What are they fighting outside?
Wait, what are they fighting outside?
Holy load.
Crazy.
Oh, that's so crazy, man.
Go go go go go go go. What is this? Not
the way in.
That was the van.
Okay,
we'll reach this and get inside and go.
Every single thing is looted.
Oh,
I see some bots.
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
Get some loot. Get out.
An Ark Orbiter is on route. The safe
window is closing. You have 10 minutes
to return to Spiranza. I repeat, 10
minutes.
>> Wait, where is the tower key? This one?
No,
bro. Everything is looted.
I don't make some I don't mind. Uh I
don't mind like fan arts. Uh, if it's
like a commission or something, I'm not
interested.
Uh, fabric
I have to get out of here,
bro. There's nothing.
I won't be adding you on Discord. Please
don't do that.
As I said, I'm not interested in
commissions. So if you're looking for
that,
I am not interested in those
This area is fully wiped clean by
everyone.
I don't think I'll find anything here,
bro. Everyone took everything.
Oh, I will need I need that.
Doll color could sell this.
Ah, this is also empty.
I'm getting a lot of junk.
I got Alexa extract, man.
>> Head home at the water treatment
elevator.
Oh [\h__\h]
Okay. Go go go go go go.
I'm never joining a ultra magnetic event
like this.
It is so chaotic.
>> All raiders arc on screen. 5 minutes
left. Go find your way home. I repeat, 5
minutes.
Wait, the leap or is there one? I die.
Wait.
385. Stop it. Stop it. Discord.
Don't shoot.
I just need to get out. Please help me
get out.
not
something.
Okay, these people were nice.
Okay, these people were nice, [laughter]
bro. [sighs and gasps]
H leveled up.
Let's see. I leveled up now. Uh,
there you go. 15
and
What should I level up next level? Next
skill point. I think I have to do this.
Uh
yeah. Yeah. Unbburden. Lol. I want to
get this. Yeah.
Conditioning.
12k.
Not much though, honestly.
I died a lot. [laughter]
I suffered a lot.
Yeah.
Advance or Oh, wait. We can sell this
metal rock. I can sell that
rubber. Why? Why do I have junk over
here?
I don't need this
processor. Headphone not needed.
Uh
uh. Not bad. Okay, let's go.
>> There's [snorts] nitrate though.
Do I need to go with this?
I want to go to the tower.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, we're okay now.
Oh, someone died here.
It's a little bit of a late raid. Okay.
here. Hope I got the right frequency.
Did you bring those grenades, Raider? My
new designs look great on paper, but
I'll need someone to chuck them at some
machines to know anything for sure.
>> By the control tower.
All
right. Go.
If I recall correctly,
there's already people here.
PvP question mark.
Hey, don't shoot.
>> [groaning]
>> Oh [\h__\h]
[groaning]
I'm going to die. I love Russians.
Hey, don't shoot.
Okay, that guy will get all the loot.
Bro,
this is my first time even coming here.
Give me something good.
Another hair.
Oh, nice
smoke in there.
I don't have heals, don't I?
Excuse
the mic here.
Appreciate it.
Oh, he just gave me a free explosive
mine blueprint.
Damn, how nice of him.
Is that Mount Fuji? Oh, that's a
mountain.
At least I used the
what do you call it?
I'm glad I at least used the
the work key or something, right?
Oh, someone already opened this.
Oh, nice. Uh, I'll replace you.
Oh, I get doll.
firework.
Oh, somebody already security breached
as well.
>> Want to go together?
Hey, want to team up?
>> What?
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
>> Uh,
>> okay.
That's the medical kit.
I could just use this.
Oh yeah, we need processors, right?
Okay.
Get those processes.
H
Ride motherboard. Um,
I'll take it. Fine.
He did not search this place. Okay, I'll
take this.
Uh
I am getting all the good stuff. I know
moderate stuff.
Humidifier.
Ah, what do I drop? Uh,
bro.
I got fired. I'll skip that.
Oh, two good stuff. Okay, fine. I'll
take I'll replace that with
another good stuff. Okay.
Wow.
Nothing.
Uh,
bandage. I
I'll take them.
Actually, I might lose them.
Oh, light bulb.
Uh,
where do I
We do need to leave though.
cracked the way.
I think we can leave.
Nice.
Not that stuff.
Fabric. Fabric.
Oh, more duckies. Nice.
Nothing here.
>> I don't
route. The safe window IS CLOSING.
10 MINUTES TO GET OUT of here.
>> Oh, nice. Uh,
>> what do I replace? Okay, switch this
14.1.
Okay, I'll take that.
Anything good over here? What is this?
Nothing.
That's better. I live
I do not want my legacy to end over
here.
Oh [\h__\h]
Bro, stop coming behind me.
Oh my god.
Stop it.
Hello Solar.
Okay, we'll go here.
Stream just lag. Hey, it happens. My PC
is dying
whenever I play the game.
It is what it is.
How you doing, Solar? It's been a while.
Don't shoot.
>> I've been doing good. Glad to hear that.
Okay, that's a good extract.
I've been doing great as well.
Fireball
41k.
There's actually 35 though.
So,
we got a couple of good guns. No,
moderate guns.
There's this This
keep that.
I'll take the healing.
We are 12 hours ahead of me. I am.
I would need this. Uh
uh
>> app.
>> What did I use 34?
I mean I'm from India so time z's on
right.
So so
23k not badium
over here and I see 1220. Yeah. Oh, so
we are to 12 hours apart.
Wow.
Crazy.
>> We are like 12 hours apart.
Sure. D
Oh,
one second everyone. I must do
something.
Okay.
Time zones, Bieber. Yes, time zones are
such a hectic.
Tada.
I am going to be paying.
Oh man,
>> battler.
or stream lag. Yeah, it lags here and
there on my PC, you know.
Can't do much about it sadly,
unfortunately.
My gunsmith. Right.
My PC lag. Oh, what's happening? What's
happening? What's happening?
I still remember that I'm not old enough
to drink and drive. [laughter]
Yeah.
Wow.
Oh, what did I do? What did I do?
That kind of shield.
Uh, where is the bandages?
Uh, okay. I have a few.
It's C. Wait, he did clip it. Oh.
Oh, that's a night raid. Okay, let's go
do a night raid.
Let's try not deny.
Oh, he did.
Speaking of shots, I have to do more
shots now.
Wow. I have to do more shots on there.
I do time to time make videos on certain
topics or my own stuff,
but yeah.
Why? So,
what do you mean?
What do you mean?
Who?
I know. I meant like general shorts. I
have to do more shorts videos time to
time. When I get any topic ideas, I do
talk about it.
Oh my god, the text is not loaded.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Have your adjusted to the dark yet.
Raider loot is ripe for the picking
while most of Toledo is asleep. Though
my suppliers say that Ark is twice as
vigilant after sunset.
>> Ah, two balls.
Scary.
Simple
player.
Ah, the ball's out.
385. What is this?
Dig a hole game. Oh, you want me to play
that?
It's been a while now.
>> Don't shoot.
Hey, don't shoot.
Who's next? Oh my god,
that's a treasure. Oh my lord.
Oh my god, my heart was beating so much.
But it's a web player.
Ah, empty
empty.
There are a lot of people here.
All of them are blueprint hiding around
there.
Um f can be five guys.
Holy. So close. So close.
It almost saw me.
Oh yeah. recently now
I've been
I've been watching I show speeds Africa
tour.
It is so nice.
Oh, come on.
Any good stuff?
Humidifier.
How do I get to here?
>> No. Bro, bro, bro, bro.
I missed my jump.
Oh no.
Oh, he's not taking the Okay, I'm going
to take it.
But there's nothing here though. Where
is he going?
Oh my god.
Uh.
Okay.
So, uh, what's the strategy? Jockn next.
Uh, oh, somebody already looted this.
No,
I wanted to come here first, but I got
trapped.
Will I get anything if I sell these
handcuff?
Oh, bulb. Yes.
Any
more good stuff I could take? Oh, gun.
Yeah, recharge shields.
Where am I going?
These guys are wiping through the map
like nothing.
I'll take a pasta.
It is so hard to be able to loot faster.
I have to learn how to loot faster.
That's the main thing, I guess.
speaker. Nope.
Going near to that.
Oh, careful. Oh, I can take this
processor sensor. Uh,
I mean I have a lot
Uh,
let's move.
Gas grenade.
Someone's extracting.
A robe.
Where are the good stuff?
Every
team up. Don't shoot.
There's three people there.
Everything is empty.
>> Hello there.
>> Hello, Raider.
>> Every single thing is empty. What the
heck?
Is that nothing?
I am unlucky
plants.
Should I extract? I have 35.
Uh,
>> use that metro entrance.
Treasures arrive. WATCH THE
>> HEY, don't shoot.
A train left.
>> Hello there.
Hello, RAIDER.
>> HELLO.
I think this guy's a gamer.
As in, why do I say that? Cuz he has
good guns behind him.
These two we bought are like basic ones.
See, see, look at his gun.
That's a pro weapon.
That's a purple epic rarity weapon.
Ah, damn. Crazy.
Uh
they're going to take a little
Wait a minute.
Uh,
I'm not having the best luck today.
That happens every single time I stream
this game. [laughter]
Is that normal? Also, um
we will be playing Fortnite soon
because Kizuna I is coming to Fortnite
on 16th.
So I ordered to play
What it again?
Here it is.
What?
And this how much? 18.
Okay, next one.
Oh, there's log gate even. Okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, let's go do the thing. Let's go do
the thing.
Download information.
Oh, wait. That's locked gate. Wait,
wait, wait, wait.
That's not the hidden bunker event.
Wait.
It has to be a hidden bunger event.
Never mind.
Matriarch.
>> I never had got an animate track. Do you
think people will replay this?
>> Imagine.
This school's not.
>> Okay, I'm going to go.
Okay.
H
update existing event
63. Where are you?
Oh, the ball.
God, I have to fix so many the
really fire.
Wow.
How to
dang it. So many issues.
New visitors off the listing
now.
Oh my.
[sighs]
Where are we?
Don't shoot.
>> Wait, what even is this again?
>> Matriarch,
>> watch your backs, Raiders. The matriarch
has been spotted near your location.
Keep your decide to go anywhere near and
always keep a close eye on her children.
>> All right.
Not much stuff.
Oh,
there's that guy.
It is that guy.
The thing is I can't damage and I don't
have a good gun.
>> Don't shoot.
It says there is a plier.
Why is that? Okay. Okay.
Duck.
[groaning]
What is that?
Is that a mat track growling?
Like if it is the matriarch. No, I would
love to fight it.
I never tried fighting it.
brother.
Oh, I better she'll recharge her. Nice.
Thank you.
It's better to get sensors from here cuz
I'm going to go
do the thing now.
Also, people are fighting the B truck.
I'll go there.
Oh, nice.
We got some good stuff.
Someone died. I could loot them.
Let me get down somehow.
I also want to find if I'm dying, what
should I take with me? Uh,
some rosemary.
Holy.
Oh, there's two of them. Small and the
big one.
Child and mother.
Hey, don't shoot.
Oh, hello. Oh my lord, it's looking at
me.
Ah,
I'm scared. I'm scared. Ah,
right.
What do I do?
I have a hair pain.
I have a stupid hair pin.
>> Don't shoot.
These guys are crazy.
I'm going to be here. I'm going to loot
them and let the M shrek once they kill
it.
I want to loot the Bastian.
And my weapon does not do anything.
Look at him doing the hellcracker.
Oh, nice.
Oh, some stuff is coming.
Is this is it a shield?
Don't mind me. I'm just going to goop.
I'm just going to goop. I'm just going
to goop.
I'm I'm just going to go. I'm just going
to go.
Oh yeah, baby. Yes. Give me more. Yes.
Run. Run.
Thank you.
the moment.
I'll keep you alive, brother.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Friendship. Oh my god.
Friendship together.
Okay. The moment. Okay. Okay. Let me put
dumb some jungle over here.
The moment we get the metric dies, goop
as fast as possible.
All right.
Oh my lord. Holy m. [crying]
That's a child over there. As in the
Thank you.
>> HEY
I really want a goop, man.
I Oh, it's going to Oh, frick.
Oh no, he died.
I'll surrender.
>> That's [\h__\h] R. Oh my god. Go go go go
go go go go.
Get the goop. Get the goop. Where is the
goop? Where is the goop? Where is the
goop,
bro? Everyone took everything.
Where? Where? Where?
Where? [screaming]
Bro, there's nothing. [groaning]
There's nothing over here. What the
heck?
Who is shooting rockets?
Oh my god.
I didn't get anything.
No, no. [laughter]
>> I didn't get anything. [laughter]
N
I do not get anything,
bro.
Bruh.
Bro,
I did not get meta.
Hey guys,
>> oh my god.
>> Sorry.
If he dies, I'm going to goop him, man.
The moment he dies, I'm going to go.
>> No.
>> Oh, no.
No.
>> Someone searching.
Brian, this guy is gooping.
Give me some goop, brother.
Uh, he took the good stuff. I swear he
took the good stuff.
>> This is absurd. I have nothing.
I have nothing.
So many people came out of nowhere.
Ah, leaper. I know what I'm going to
leave, man.
>> Head home at the central elevator.
>> Oh my god.
An arc orbiter is on route. The safe
window is closing.
>> Okay, that's closed.
>> I repeat, 10 minutes.
Hello.
>> Wait, someone actually opened it. Oh,
someone actually opened it.
Ah, I did not get the queen um
matriarch stuff though.
Wow, I didn't get the matriarch man.
That's a bit odd [music] and
help.
This guy was helping a lot, right? Who
is this?
I got a lot of co [laughter]
a lot of co.
Okay, drink some water everyone.
I have 14.
The torren. [laughter] Oh my god. I'm
going to save this
to
yours.
>> Can't believe I got a torrentail just
like that.
Ah, and that's still a battery.
Oh, still.
What the
Where did it go? Okay. Wait.
Mother
game discussion.
Okay. So, I'm supposed to take
uh
Yeah, this thing.
Oh, so much deadlines.
Not going to even use these.
Is it still there? Okay, Kav can go join
another one.
I want to take some
I want to take uh plenty of heals this
time.
Arc basel. I don't have it. Uh,
good to see you again.
I have to get more arc power cell.
I have five. I have a lot of anvils. I
can just take one anvil now.
I mean, we're literally going to be
gooping. So,
>> I'm lucky. I'm lucky.
>> Okay, let's go, Matria.
Let's go, Goop. [laughter]
It's always going to be in the
centermost area. Spaceport area. No, the
tower launch tower area. No, the
matriarch.
I got it like that.
Oh my god, so many mosquitoes. Wow.
And my cross play crossplay is off.
That's why my load time like
the queue times are a bit longer because
the crossplay is off now.
So there's that.
Okay, let's see.
Add a break.
Oh, we finally got a game.
Let's go.
Finally got a game.
Wait, it's still mat track, right? We
had a longer wait Q time
if it's out. Oh no,
please be my truck.
Oh, it is. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Get
to the launch tower.
>> Let's go to the launch towers.
>> Before that, we'll need to scout some
stuff.
But they already started.
>> Don't shoot. Feel
like some people started
>> Oh, it's here.
Where is she head? I see some bridges
over there.
Oh, it's southeast. No, southwest.
>> Don't shoot.
Are they going to lower it or something?
Oh, it's over there.
>> Oh, they're fighting over there.
See how many people are going
mana. Uh oh, they put the
>> Is it to stream? Oh.
Holy Lord, I almost died.
My god.
Oh my god.
Bro,
bro.
Oh, it's so frustrating.
I got nothing.
There's nothing, bro.
Aren't these matra stuff?
Please be matrix or
beep. All of them took the loot, bro.
Come on. Keep some for me.
Oh nah.
N.
Oh my lord. Holy m Another
leaper going there.
What the [\h__\h]
still nice [\h__\h]
Oh god.
>> [groaning]
>> Oh [\h__\h]
We locked eyes.
Oh my lord.
Ah, shield.
Oh, gucky. Ah.
The moment it dies, I'm going to go in.
Okay, it's going to blow up any moment
now.
We are going to goop.
Okay. Go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
baby. Go go go go go go go go go go go
baby.
Where is [screaming] it?
Bro, everyone is loading.
There's nothing.
There's nothing,
>> bro.
There's nothing.
>> What the heck?
What the hell?
What the hell? Why?
Not
>> my first time.
>> [\h__\h] man. I didn't have anything. And I
kill him.
>> So nice.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Thank you. My first
two more literally I need two more. Give
me give me more. Give me one more.
>> What? But how to use this this material
for
let's get this this weapon.
919.
[laughter]
>> Hello guys.
Thank you.
>> Damn, this the whole busy. Hey guys. Oh
gosh.
>> Hello.
>> Oh my god.
Brh. [laughter]
Brh.
Oh, bruh.
Bro, not for nothing.
There was nothing.
The amount of game. Okay, this person
was on Twitch. I want to check them on
Twitch.
Uh, mare
What the
j
manus?
There's no one named man. What the? Oh,
I think I saw I see I see I see you.
It's a YouTuber.
Uh,
it was a YouTuber.
so
baby
Look at 26.
Oh god. Oh,
we didn't get much. [laughter]
We did not get much.
I like this.
We didn't get anything.
And I I was taking damage a lot.
Now the main truck event is gone. How
rooster event is there?
Oh,
also what time is it?
Where should I wrap up for today? It was
a short stream, too. So,
so yeah,
it was a short stream, too. this uh
so we'll wrap it up here, I guess.
But I have a big stash issue though.
So many things.
Uh
how do I show
Stash is show
Ailion. Oh, I need to get one matriarch.
Ailion.
Our road is one.
Oh, look. So, needed for the deadline.
Ah, yeah.
I got triggered though.
Oh, you can even craft power rods.
That's nice.
And this thing as well. Well, you need
other uh
>> crazy motion core.
Mhm.
Off this drill.
Blue light stick, red stick, yellow
stick. Is there no green stick?
Uh,
stash issue.
I mean for regarding the stash, I can
just put it here now.
Wow.
these stuff. Uh
Water will do.
ire items. Have to put a lot of guns.
I don't want to remove these guns. It's
still honestly
[laughter] it's just 100
VP.
28k.
Okay.
No. Uh
oh. Uh I haven't wait. Uh
Hi. Yeah, but I'll go to sleep soon
though. I'm wrapping up though.
Binocular. Uh, I don't need it.
I can sell this.
Uh, we need more space.
Patrol car. Rear door of a patrol car.
What?
Oh, not petrol. Patrol. Okay.
2,00
100 100,000.
I think if I give it a lot of assorted
seeds. No. Isn't that better?
Mushrooms also gives me 10k
rocketeer.
I do 3 4 5 6 9 10 9 12 13 whatever. H
I'll settle this.
Uh
Ashim,
it is late.
Uh frying pan
moss.
I need a motor now.
This is almost million. 1 mil, right?
Three. Um,
uh, 350.
Uh, a mat. I think this is one mil, uh,
of items.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. The event is
done, right? Like Oh yeah. Yeah. Only a
few 12 hours left. Tomorrow it'll be
gone.
Uh
>> fix today.
If I get any better at small talk, I'm
going to need to open flatter.
Ah,
yeah. Flutter and stuff is so high.
>> Oh, it's you forcer.
It does so much damage. Oh, okay. If I
wanted window shopping, I'd have
>> I want to buy, but I'm broke. I have to
get unleashed at a million.
I need to get to 5 mill though.
>> Hey, we will wrap it up over here.
Uh, it's going to be too sleep.
Uh,
I
Oh,
how did it go?
Sleep. Hello, Bacon.
Man, honestly, Bacon, I feel like I'm so
unlucky. Like I I joined three or two
matriarch events and I didn't get
anything.
Bro, why am I
Why am I
so unlucky whenever I stream this game?
Is it because I lack the PC equipment uh
to play it properly? Cuz it lags a lot
when I stream.
I don't know. I don't get it. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. is doing Python course. Now
I'm joining the um the basic financial
uh com that com that basic commerce
thing you know how to um cost counting
and all those stuff. I'm doing that. I'm
going to do that. I mean since doing
that taking the class so
um
I'm going to to take that. Well, I lost
when did I lost my snap. Oh, well, it
was bad. [laughter]
Ah, snap.
Show down there.
Yeah, there's a car. All right, I'll be
here in a little bit.
Wow,
okay. Uh, where is the ad? Let me wait
till the ad is back. The ad is over,
then I'll repeat. Okay, don't worry.
Okay, I was trying to Yeah. Yeah, I read
that. I read that.
Okay. I was saying that yeah I'm joining
the finance class which I mean since
taking after the net exam is over on
18th. Oh yeah, my exam is on January
18th and [music] not for Q4.
Yesterday, what did I do?
I thought finance there's a basic
accountancy class happen uh course they
are doing for cost counting and stuff
for surviv not survivability like uh
like how to I mean going to Japan you'll
learn uh how to balance your money
finances and stuff so you don't get
broke broke that easily cuz everywhere
anywhere you see it's you easily lose
money so quickly. Okay. No, I can't skip
university. I have to do university now.
I have to transfer my credits
credits into a new university and check.
So, I'll probably write a new exam from
the embassy, Indian embassy in Japan cuz
you can write from there if with special
permission.
Yeah. What was I doing yesterday?
I didn't play Arc. Yeah,
how could I join you? I can
we don't need any more than for
apparently. Oh, you know
that is so nice.
me.
Okay, I have to fix the Discord even
create button. The live stream ID needs
to be an array. That stuff,
so many things. Oh,
I'll worry about it later. Uh, but yeah,
I
did some stuff for the squad. Um,
uh, I updated the upcoming streams
thingy.
Uh, well, let me I can I show them. What
the
Oh, yeah. Yesterday I was doing this.
That's why they couldn't play arc. Oh
yeah. And now it hit me. Oh yeah.
[gasps]
Oh yeah. That's why. Oh yeah.
Oh yeah. So I updated the upcoming
stream. Before it was like this embed. I
made it into like this.
So if there's more than six stream
scheduled, it will be in a compat list.
It won't be like this with a button.
It'll be like a text uh thingy, you
know. Yeah. And I finally made automated
our announcement thingy.
So yeah, when I'm live, it will say
this. And also it has a stream preview
as well. So this triggers f every 10
minutes. This patch patch event happens
every 10 minutes. Don't mind this. This
was a test stream. Yeah, I'll fix that.
How could you stream the game normally?
I don't know.
I actually don't know. [gasps and sighs]
Uh that's a good question. Like see
this. I don't know if you can see it. Oh
yeah, you can see it. see this. I'm
currently streaming on my 24x7 channel,
too. How in the world was I able to
like I don't know like
memory wise it is. Oh yeah, it closed
the game, right? I don't get it. But
sometimes it works, sometimes it doesn't
work. I don't get it.
Oh boy.
But yeah, uh this is done. Uh the next
thing I have to do is patch all of these
older streams and say make it say stream
as ended and stuff
all those stuff. Uh I have to
work on the finalizer button which is
this.
And then the last one I think by that
time everything these 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
nine nine stuff I've been it's been 3
months now I've been focusing on this
bro [gasps] it's finally over.
Yeah.
Uh
okay demo
kaisha
Yeah.
I think he should go for a foreign
company.
Me too. I think I don't think I'll be
able to
um I don't think I'll be able to work in
a Japanese company. I'll die here.
[laughter]
And they're super strict and so much
pain. So I don't think I will ever do
that. Nope. Nope. Nope.
Wow.
Speaking of which, uh I think I need a
So, I'm thinking if I should do more
streams this week cuz exam is happening
on Sunday and I have to leave by Friday.
So, today's it's already Tuesday. So, 1
2 3 I have three more days. So, I was
thinking maybe I'll do less streams.
uh
last stream. So, just 1 hour of stream.
Okay. And uh yeah, 1 hour of stream and
then I'll just um
I don't know if I should stream
uh the Japanese thing. I mean, I would
love to do the Japanese thingy like the
textbook now. Try invert textbook from
start to scratch. I I want I would love
to do it 24x7. I would love to do that.
I wouldn't mind, but I would love to do
it on stream. Uh yeah.
So
I would love to choke.
Uh stream wasn't steady. Yeah, the thing
is if I don't stream or if I just The
thing is I get pro I procrastinate a
lot. I'll be doing something else. I
should be literally be doing an stuff
daily. I haven't not been doing that
properly and that's bad. I'm already the
weakest in the class already. Um cuz
lack of practice I the kanji thingy I
have to start working on it. But yeah,
Ank is the only thing which going to
save me when it come comes to consumer.
But yeah, shame monkey. Yeah, good idea.
Good idea. I should do that. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I should do that. And
whenever the thing comes now, I'll write
it down in a notebook or something or uh
like Canva or like paint. Keep on
writing writing writing. Whenever the
prompt comes, then I'll put hard. Then
when the next time it uh switches and
comes then I will not forget. Now I'll
do that actually. Okay. Tomorrow on
Wednesday we are going to do.
Yeah.
Yeah. I'll do that.
Yeah. Yeah. I should actually be writing
my answers. Yeah.
Yeah. Long stroke too. Yeah.
The thing is not due to the time
constraints I can't
like give more time right now
right exam is close so I have to like be
ultra
uh paka paka with like with grammar all
those stuff so I will have to like yeah
I mainly do the try and for book and do
the work work book questions in the
behind the behind back page of that PDF
or book.
Yeah, I'll I'll have to do those
then I'm surely I'll pass. Yeah. after
the thing is I have to plan out a steady
uh schedule after my exams are over on
18th Sunday right Monday onwards 19th
onwards I have to sit down
practice Anki practice the kanji order
stroke order everything from the
beginning daily at least 1 hour if I can
give it no then by by March and stuff
I'll be I'll be do it. Yeah, I'll be
able to do stuff.
Yeah. Yeah.
But that's my game plan. But the thing
is I I don't want to be all talk and no
action. So I have to do the make it
happen properly
schedule everything and do it. Yeah.
Okay, it's going to be uh how long
again?
Okay, I have three more minutes and I'll
go.
Hi.
I'm glad I still remember the Nuji.
I thought she was shin.
Wait, that's that that's not [laughter]
Oh my god. Wait.
Shinu. Oh yeah. Oh my [gasps] god. Okay.
Sorry. Sorry. Yeah.
[laughter]
Okay.
Hi. It was really fun. I I I don't
stream at this time. I used to stream at
this time when I was playing do it night
a [\h__\h] Right.
But yeah, Kuna ice skin is coming on
Fortnite. So, I'll play Fortnite when it
drops. 16th, right? Oh, wait.
16. Ah, I won't be there on 16th.
I'm going
by night today to for exam. Yeah,
the ball
16. Okay, I'll stream Fortnite on 19th
then after exam. Yeah. Yeah, that'll be
better. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Anyway, uh yeah, we'll wrap up. It's
already 2:00 a.m. Going to be 2:00 a.m.
Hi. Hi. Hi.
That's it. Thank you to
I'll stream again.
Uh,
I'll I'll I'll stream again in the
future. Probably tomorrow.
Not sure. But yeah.
Anyhow, take care you guys. Have a good
one. Bye-bye.